Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame, but the chats on fire can't take
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot
flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting gong Alex taking flight
it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night he's got him simping hearts in the
chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the
girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo yo yo Michael
Drop the line, gong, not tonight
Alex tried to joke, boom, sent into the night
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike
Diamonds feeling spicy, shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says, with a wink, that's the whole show
Sighs half asleep, but still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon, so glow
No rules, just roles, we pretend to play
One
We're trending in the press
The vibe
She whispers and flames
Please hide and seek with the shadows
Restream beat the don't be mean didn't know that my mistakes would turn the whole scene green
I mentioned Tracy and poor Michael song now. I'm writing you this anthem just to right that wrong
So lay off me a little bit. I'm begging on my knees your critiques rain down harder than a hurricane breeze
I don't want to feel worthless don't want to feel small be to take your foot off my neck. That's all
made that art I thought it was rad didn't know it would make you so mad now I'm
walking around like a guilty pup every time
Hey, what's up? Sorry. How are you?
Yeah
Longs, what's everyone doing? Hey, Jamie. How are you? Oh my god, I made him work some more
That's pretty cool. I like that
I got nervous today, I'll show you something, there we go, see the logo for my, that is
actually the logo for, the new logo for my Etsy store which I have like now
There, I have to go and check. I mean, I have only two put up right now.
I'm almost got the third put up. And I'm going to try out this.
I mean, it's like, of course, I don't know if I'm like, you know, I have to elaborate on the descriptions and things like that,
but I mean, they're going to be really awesome of course.
And you can check out my, like,
Reviews on Etsy and everything. I have almost like over a thousand. I have over a thousand reviews and
They're pretty positive but uh one second, let me see my next store
And they are priced pretty high, but you know
I do plan on over providing, and also for, let's really make a, oh yeah, I'll put a big
discount on it.
Like I'll put it like, they'll always be on sale, you know, probably, and then I'll give
you, I'll give people in chat a few, or members, I'll give you the bigger discount, I'll give
An extra extra 25% off so that's like 75% off anything from members one that's that'd be pretty good deal
Of course, I'll do a pretty good reports for everybody too
So yeah, I'm just trying to resurrect store a little bit
because
It's to get actually it was really good for that period of time
I do want to do now. I will put it
I think I need to put like a video reading all and more stuff as it goes along
I'm just trying to get some, you know, and maybe I made a mistake when I'm on YouTube
and stuff, like trying to, you know, be on YouTube and then it's like, you know, not
well hopefully things will turn around I think that uh...
I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh... I think that uh...
this morning. What day is it? It's a Monday. Sunday. It's Sunday today. Well, let's see.
Oh, I need to like, vlog another account. Vlogging the wrong one. Okay, sign in. Cool.
I hope this is the right one, let's see, I can't put it up, what can I get in my account?
Okay, okay, I can't see it.
Okay, good, yeah, okay, here it is.
So how do I show you my store?
A little bit rusty on the, like the, oh here we go, okay.
this is the store oh yeah that's pretty cool it still is pretty good I think I'm
gonna redo the banner and stuff but yeah it looks pretty damn good you have a
look at it hold on I'll go back to the chat
the only the only one I have to put on is a more expensive one
Wait, there's like nobody here or like it's a really like oh hey, what's up guys? Okay? Here's my link right here
I'm gonna check it out. I'll put every half 50% on it. I think but I need to put more good morning
It's the best Sunday so far. Yeah, it's early. So it's like well. Yeah, I don't know
I'm ready to go
But that looks pretty cool. I like like I like the logo I made
There's really you guys my helpful logo or anything I can make you really cool
I feel like that one or my other one too, it's like oh, the other one is pretty cool.
What happens to everybody?
I'm a little bit slow on this game, I'm just a little bit too much pop this part.
Okay, so the other one is right here.
This is for my main.
That is like the Medisakey.
And it's like there's like labyrinth things that I'm part of it. I have a horse. I love it. I love it just like some of that stuff
Incorporated together and it's like a certain source. I
Totally cool. Let's see. What else do I got?
You know I'm trying to have like some stuff I can like you know try to like
trying to incorporate more. I don't know what I want to share with you guys right now.
You know, on some crazy... I'll show you what I look good at.
I was like, I'm trying to think of everything. This is what I think of when I'm like, okay, can you like,
You know, put someone like watching the show. Do you see it? Oh, yeah
It's like someone watching my show dance to the mystery I think
I think I think I think I don't think in a bad way. I think it's like
She's a nice Canadian witch, you know, so he's very nice
I don't think she means any harm. Hopefully not. I hope she's just watching my show. Just be pleasant. But I don't know
You gotta be sure there's somebody to point it at make sure
Hey, what's up J-Doc? How are you? Good morning?
So guys, I don't know if you've heard but I do have an apology song. I give the beat an apology song, but I've been playing one version and I'll play the other one.
Are you guys interested in hearing the beat an apology song?
There you go. I need to put a picture of beat it up so I'll do it. See, I think we'll do this one.
I dare to do with it.
Is that good?
Okay, I'm sorry, I know I'm going a little overboard, but I only have like a few credits left
So I don't have like two songs I can make I think until I buy more credits, but
That's good coffee and then I get that I must have gotten that this morning, but I fell asleep
How is it?
730 I
Was didn't sleep for very long been on promotion hour
Okay, it's it opens at 6 o'clock. What time is it? It's only 730 the heck
Hi guys, how's everybody doing?
It's funny like I said, yeah, I don't know it's like I think my show looks so much better and it's like
There's people here being seven people. It's fine
But I mean earlier when I was in this chat like everyone could think people kept coming in and leaving
But it's like I think it was because I'm playing a song but or
Yes, I'm not playing instruments or singing the music on that on those songs, but I'm
Concepts of them. I mean unless I mean
And it's pretty good though, you know improvising on some things, but for the most part I put everything
So anyway, and
That like be that I don't know she said it doesn't look like I think it might I
Didn't use her it is off of her face like a prop of one of the other videos from the trip
Blurs
No, this moves up. Sorry.
I will just take this down.
I'm gonna reverse my image and it will look better.
Now it's kind of correct, but look.
While we're up here, oh there I am.
Can I do that?
Oh my god.
Can I do the other one?
like that oh there but I have to be next to myself like that ah I do and I don't want to show my
kitchen like that oh my god show these people how that's interesting
let's see it's really cool I haven't been I don't have like my my headphones and normal
And so it's kind of like crazy.
Hi everybody, where is everybody?
No one's gonna like come hang out with me anymore?
Probably should be the last night.
You promised not to say anything bad about her.
I mean I didn't say anything bad about her
and she still was mad.
I wasn't even like making fun of her or anything on that thing.
Then she got me all mad and now I've like
made like three songs about her so far.
Maybe our movie never we're not friends. I don't know
I thought I talked to where I was on Sam and so and it didn't go very well
Anyway, it's getting a little bit too depressing if nobody if nobody comes up six people I know
Well, I think I don't know. I think I really it's funny and I don't know the YouTube show. I don't think it's gonna go
longer I think maybe this is a quiet day or something like that but I mean it's
like everybody hates me on YouTube like what then that's what I kind of feel
like sometimes it's like you're like you know five people everywhere it's gonna
use you and throw in the towel kind of it's too hard look at all these people
Oh, I'm not going to give up, but I'm just going to say some case.
Because I do have someone's drive to do this show, and I love to do this show.
Man, it's hard sometimes.
I love that
Pretty cool
I think that will be that will look so great and embroidery on like merchandise and I really do think I'll have good merchandise
And I really
Trying to like get all my all my like my website
Done and so I can have like, you know all my stuff linked. Oh my god. It's gonna be so cool
If I can finally get it done and like invite actually like
You know, I just worry like just this is the time where it's like oh shit
I guess it's like never have gone on that a YouTube show because now
like
people hate me
I got a ring and
I do
Look into the void
come with me together
it really would be great if you guys would like me to consider a membership
or something
oh yeah yeah
so we have a
Anyway, I guess I'll try to do some of the clips so long.
Okay guys are you ready? I have some clips. Are you ready for the clips? You like it?
Promise you like it.
Share screen. Okay, this is shocking.
Uh-oh, let's check it out.
I'm just saying
Yeah, I think that's hot as shit. I just woke up. I think Vita has seen his I think he showed his penis to Vita before I think he was
She was like odd in the phone with him and he showed her and
She said she screamed but he should that she's
She screamed you think she screamed I think she was she was traumatized man
You know, I don't know if she's gonna go get Vita man. Let it come over like come over
She was she was she was traumatized. I mean, who would
In Louisiana because I'm gonna go visit her. She says she'll make me some gumbo. She says that
With your girlfriends, you're gonna cheat with her with big Nisha
Imagine
But the one with Nisha is like a month ahead
And I haven't told my girlfriend about Big Misha because I don't know how she'll take it
Well, I don't think she'll be I should we're gonna be just friends right you're just friends
Yeah, she's pretty cool. If that's the same girl you know with last time she's pretty chill
All the boundaries are coming down
Big Misha is like 500 pounds though, so I don't know
Big mission yet. She's pouring
He looks like he has a jar on his head right now.
I can talk about shit.
Really?
That's how you got it?
That's what we don't need.
That nigga teeth look like sunflower seeds.
You have to be 16 years old.
How about you banging on some shit?
Get the fuck out of here, loser.
Oh, no.
Fuck.
I got another one.
I got another funny.
I
Got some advice for you, man stay at a dirty tools at night. I'm out
Well, it's funny because he says shit with the camera off though
Yeah, no for hours. I leave your channel like several times
Let's see. Can you say my channel one time tonight or so? You say just things like you're waking
You know, you have to say any good anything more
Just mention the channel my channel name. Is that too much to ask?
That's all I ask
It's too much. It's okay. I understand.
I'm like, aw, how cute.
She said it.
I'm saying, Saki, why, why, why you kill my mic, Saki?
Uh, a lot of the paulers, paulers.
Yeah, everybody get freaky up here.
Yeah. Um.
Okay.
Hi for only 499 minutes.
If you call this number, I told you.
You're fucking, um.
You can do that, isn't that pie?
Yeah, you can do it.
Amber going back to her old ways, man.
You're crazy.
That's how she got her husband.
That's a pretty good deal for you.
Shut up!
You only two minutes, Aldo.
That's 10 dollars.
You know who would be the top three donators?
It would be fucking us.
Sandman number one.
fucking up bury the turtle
Elbow
No, of course it's not of course enough because don't we know what that was gonna happen
I'd say everything was correlated, you know whether you I didn't whether you like it or not, right? I didn't fucking enjoy what happened
No, there goes Bronzeberg, okay.
Bidgey, are you fucking serious right now?
Bidgey, you're back now.
Are you fucking serious right now?
You can do it running your mouth like this?
Please, please tell me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
because have you checked out my channel?
I'm starting to go live stream.
I will beat your fucking ass on the ground.
Yeah, let's meet up on the street.
Let's meet up on the street.
Bring him back.
No, no, no, I got a question for him.
Are you straight making threats to me?
No, no, no, I got a question.
Where?
Where do you want me to meet?
Oh, I'll go over right now.
They make you fudge.
You know when you're in a date late last night I was out with my girl and then I
We're not at the stage where I can just part freely
When she has to go I'm like, yeah, thank goodness and then I just fucking rape as it
And then I, you know what I was doing to conceal the sound, I turned the water closet on, because she was in the bathroom and I was in the water closet.
Exactly, yep.
It's fucking ripped out and I was like, alright, as we were.
Yeah, in the beginning it was a relationship.
in the beginning, not even in the beginning of her life, I feel like as, I think you get
comfortable in just this one, some years in the comfort and you're able to just part in front of
your late partner, like that's, that's when you know they, huh, they, where, where in this?
Oh, it's true love, you know, true love. That's true love, exactly. We're
You know what I mean? So, I think that maybe he is into that.
You like to be treated like a dog.
Maybe, yeah.
Have you done research?
On?
Have you done your research? Like, have you messaged them and like try, like, try to like treat them like a dog?
Or are you just like making it like a dog?
I'm not trying to, like, uh, be fainting.
I do research on fetishes.
I know a lot about fetishes, and I know that as a fetish,
people like some people are in, will pay to be disrespected.
So you like eating a little bit?
You like, you like albino peanuts?
Like, what do you want?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just grown.
I'm gonna sell them to other people.
I don't know who.
You don't put the albino peanuts in your mouth?
If I did, I would never tell you about it, and not in this setting, my friend.
It conducts wars in non-lethal and non-destructive ways.
Essentially, you overwhelm your enemy with arguments.
You seize control of all the means by which is government and populist process information.
to make up their minds and you adjust it so those minds are made up as you desire everyone is happy
no one gets hurt or killed and nothing is destroyed ordinary warfare on the other hand is oh where I
can it can't go where you think you run bro that's nothing
I remember one time, I remember where you said that you threw up like an exit off the freeway.
An exit off the freeway.
Yeah.
No, it's not funny.
What?
I do think it's funny.
It's really not.
I cried last night.
I want you to unmod me.
I don't think that it's funny that you're doing this.
You're calling me a witch.
I get badgered all the time being called a witch.
You don't sorry me to be there. I got you back
It's good
I thought you were spinning around and we did the clips up
What do you want to talk about
Bait it came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking bout biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran
Where's the honey sauce, girl it's gone
You say you're the queen of the big off crew
But your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rosewater drizzle
You brought confusion and a half baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon
I don't know what she's talking about, but when she says, like,
that song's insulting, because it's such a cute song, and it's not insulting at all.
Well, it is a little bit insulting, but it's not like...
She doesn't talk about teeth falling out.
I don't know what she's talking about when she's like,
Oh, it's talking about my teeth falling out?
I don't remember ever saying anything like that, or my pain.
I don't know what she's talking about.
If you guys figure it out, let me know.
It's like it's kind of slowed down today, or maybe I think everyone's maybe at the church of Sam and today, but maybe I'll
I think I like to skip church, but I'll play this out in a song
And thanks guys for coming though
Sorry, it wasn't more fun
We'll try next time
I
What?